Farris Family Papers﻿ SC1374
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Farris Family Papers﻿
1908-1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1374
3 Linear Feet (2 cartons)
Content Description
Correspondence, photographs, diaries, and ephemera.
Biographical / Historical
Fauna Wynne “Pat” Farris and Edna Esther Ingles Farris both earned A.B. degrees in English from Stanford University in May 1917. They were married in 1920.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
World War, 1914-1918.; Aeronautics -- History.; Postcards.; Diaries.
- Biographical material
  - Michael Neher. Pat Farris, the aviator from Stockton (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biographical clippings (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence
  - Edna to Pat
    - Edna to Pat, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Edna to Pat, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Edna, love story to Pat, pre-1920 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Edna to Pat, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Edna to Pat, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pat to Edna
    - Pat to Edna, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Pat to Edna, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Pat to Edna, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Pat to Edna, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Pat to Edna, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Pat to Edna, 1940 Jun-Jul (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Pat to Edna (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Pat to Edna, 1940 Aug-Sep (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Pat to Edna, 1940 Oct (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Pat to Edna, 1940 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Pat to Edna (Aviation school, Fort Worth), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ruth to parents, 1934
    - Ruth to parents, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Diaries
  - FWF diary, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - FWF diary, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Edna E. Farris diary, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Edna E. Farris diary, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Edna E. Farris diary, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Photographs
  - Aviation
    - Aerial survey photos, circa 1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Edna Esther Farris, Letterman Hospital, SF (Presidio), circa 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Boeing C47, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Curtiss JN-4D, 1918-1920 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Marine aviation, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Pat and Edna; Curtiss JN-4D, 1918; 1920 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fairchild 71, circa 1930s (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - International F-18 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Junkers F13, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Various aircraft (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Edna Esther (Ingels) Farris, Curtiss JN-4D, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Personal
    - Peter Flores, Guatemala, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Pat Farris and clients (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - World War I
    - Captain Joe Foss (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pat Farris, WWI - France, Alabama, Greece, 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Letterman Hospital, circa 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - WW1 - France, Albania, Greece, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - WW1 - France, Albania. Contact prints and negatives, circa 1917 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Dijon (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - WW1 - France, souvenir photos (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - WW1 - Souvenir photos (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - FW Farris, Besancon, France, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Postcards
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Albania (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - France (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Becancon (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dijon (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - French countryside (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Marseille (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Greece (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Records
  - EEF address book, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Birthdates book, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Children's growth books (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Stanford Commencement program, 1917 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Edna Ingels - HS diploma, Fresno, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Poem (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - W.H. Tribette Will, Trust documents, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous documents (Box 2, Folder 43)